let qa = [
    { question : "Which is an improper CSS width?",
      answers :  [
        "width: vw;",
        "max-width: 25%;",
        "min-width: absolute;",
        "width: initial;"
      ],
      correct : "min-width: absolute;"
    },
    { question : "What is the most popular Javascript server-library?",
      answers :  [
        "NodeJS",
        "ReactJS",
        "GoLang",
        "Django"
      ],
      correct : "NodeJS"
    },
    { question : "Which of these is not a CSS preprocessor?",
      answers :  [
        "SASS",
        "LESS",
        "Handlebars",
        "Stylus"
      ],
      correct : "Handlebars"
    },
    { question : "____ divide applications into separated files of related ideas for a more managable structure.",
      answers :  [
        "Modules",
        "<div>'s",
        "Noobs",
        "Components"
      ],
      correct : "Modules"
    },
    { question : "Which of these is the best definition of an algorithm?",
      answers :  [
        "An audio visualizing program closely linked to the rythm of music.",
        "A programmatic set of instructions to solve a problem.",
        "A program error that results in an infite loop.",
        "A method of organization for pair programming."
      ],
      correct : "A programmatic set of instructions to solve a problem."
    },
    { question : "Which HTTP method is most commonly associated with submitting a form?",
      answers :  [
        "GET",
        "PUT",
        "POST",
        "PATCH"
      ],
      correct : "POST"
    },
    { question : "What does API stand for?",
      answers :  [
        "Application Processing Interpreter",
        "Associated Programming Inspector",
        "Application Programming Interface",
        "Asynchronous Point Inheritance"
      ],
      correct :
        "Application Programming Interface"
    },
    { question : "To perform a repetitive task given a single condition you would use...",
      answers : [
        "A loop",
        "An array",
        "Internet Explorer",
        "A boolean"
      ],
      correct : "A loop"
    },
    { question : "In the SQL query 'SELECT age FROM users', which column is being selected?",
      answers : [
        "SELECT",
        "age",
        "FROM",
        "users"
      ],
      correct: "age"
    },
    { question : "In JavaScript how do you create a variable that cannot be reassigned?",
      answers : [
        "var x = 'hello'",
        "let x = 'hello'",
        "string x = 'hello'",
        "const x = 'hello'"
      ],
      correct: "const x = 'hello'"
    }
  
  ]